Before moving on to the impact libraries, the lateral movement section, we need to modify
fewer registry keys on the machine to enable a few of the features to enable or disable
few of the features in modern Microsoft operating system.
Basically, before the Windows 10, some of the hot fix, we do not need to execute, we
do not need to modify these registry keys.
It will be normally enabling the guest access or remote administration.
Let me show you one by one.
If you are using a new operating system or if your target is a new operating system
and it is a modern operating system, you need to enable allow insecure guest auth.
So basically, it will enable the guest access to the file share with the insecure protocols
like SMB.
In the impact command, the basically impact command will be creating or modifying some
services or executable in the adventure or a seizure folders in the windows.
So our account needs to access that adventure and seizure with insecure protocol SMB
or something.
To do that, we need to enable the guest access in the network share.
So this command will basically give you do that thing.
You need to open the command prompt in the administrator mode and you need to execute
this command, I will be giving this command lines and the resource section or the end
of the last video in this section.
So do not worry about that.
So you can execute this.
So you need to execute these three commands in the machine.
So this command is to sit the firewall of maybe we are connecting towards the 4/4/5 or
SMB or some kind of network protocol.
So at that time the firewall will monitor our connection and it will block our connection.
So we are turning off the firewall and we are doing some kind of UAC restriction because
the local administrator account needs to go for remote administrator mode to perform the
malicious activity to disable the UAC restriction.
These are access control restriction we are modifying this registry.
This three commands you need to execute before pushing the next video.
I hope you have a clear understanding about this 3 commands and once you start picking
up the next video, you can have an idea why we executed this command.
So let's hop off from here and we'll continue our discussion on next video.
See you guys.
Bye.